Hello, my name is Goody,
你好，我叫 Goody，
and in 1841, I was bitten by a stem vampire.
1841年，我被一个吸血鬼咬了。
A stem is able to awaken the victims
他不吸干受害者
they choose not to drain.
从而唤醒他们
Normally, this would be one of those tales
通常情况下，这将是其中一个故事
of gore and homicidal urges,
充满血腥和杀人冲动，
but I've always looked on the bright side.
但我一直在寻找 从好的方面来看。
So I learned to live on animal blood.
所以我学会通过动物血液生存
And having eternal life
并永生
gave me extra years with my loved ones.
让我能与所爱之人多相处几年。
Nighttime used to be dull and dark,
夜晚曾经是沉闷而黑暗的，
but things got a lot better in the '80s.
但到了 80 年代情况好多了。
Oh, the 1880s, that is.
哦，那是 19 世纪 80 年代。
The Industrial Revolution gave us electricity
工业革命给我们带来了电力
and light bulbs.
和灯泡。
And suddenly, nights were as bright as daytime.
突然间，夜晚变得如同白天一样明亮。
Telephones replaced letters,
电话取代了信件，
and the new subways let you travel the whole city
新的地铁可以让你游览整个城市
and still be in your coffin by sunrise.
到日出时你仍会躺在棺材里。
In the 1920s, things really turned modern.
在 20 世纪 20 年代，事情确实变得现代化了。
Skirts got shorter,
裙子变短了，
jazz babies and flappers owned the night.
爵士宝贝和轻佻女郎主宰了整个夜晚。
The world belonged to the young,
世界属于年轻人，
and I was an expert at being young.
我非常擅长应对年轻人。
And then came my favorite invention--
然后我最喜欢的发明来了——
flickers.
闪烁。
Chaplin, Keaton, Cagney--
卓别林、基顿、卡格尼——
and in movies, they never got any older.
而在电影中，他们却从未变老。
I could relate.
我也能理解。
In the 1960s, I messed up.
20 世纪 60 年代，我搞砸了。
I let my guard down
我放松了警惕
After that, things started to go downhill.
此后，事情开始走下坡路。
In the '70s, I kinda lost interest in dating.
到了 70 年代，我对约会有点失去了兴趣。
But in the '90s, my stem turned Stacy.
但在 90 年代，我唤醒了 Stacy。
She was kind of lost and I took care of her.
她有点失落，我照顾她。
I taught her to get hometown soil for her coffin,
我教她取家乡的泥土做棺材，
how to use hypnotic powers,
如何使用催眠力量，
and how to find the jugular on a rodent.
以及如何找到啮齿动物的颈静脉。
And she taught me about e-mail,
她教我如何使用电子邮件，
Napster, and this great group,
Napster 和伟大的
Green Day.
绿日乐队。
So we have lots of fun.
因此我们玩得很开心。
We party with normal kids, we go to college.
我们和普通孩子一起聚会，一起上大学。
I've got over 10,000 credits.
我已经获得超过 10,000 个积分。
I could graduate if it wasn't during the day.
如果不是白天的话我就能毕业了。
I love having a friend,
我喜欢有个朋友，
or "bestie," as she calls it.
或者用她的话说就是“闺蜜”。
And, aw, look how cute she is.
噢，看看她多可爱啊。
Hey, Goody.
嘿，Goody。
Goody, wake up. It's sunset.
好家伙，醒醒。太阳落山了。
The only bad thing about Stacy
Stacy 唯一的缺点
are her practical jokes,
是她的恶作剧，
which she thinks are way funnier than they actually are.
她认为这些故事比实际情况有趣得多。
What?
什么？
No, you didn't.
不，你不能这么做。
Come on, let me out.
拜托，放我出去。
- You got me - Again.
- 真是被你打败了 - 又一次。
Hurry, I've got an 8:00 class.
快点，我8点有课。
Hey, Stacy. Your friend from Boston
嘿，Stacy。你波士顿的朋友
sent your hometown soil.
寄给你家乡的泥土。
Oh, thank God.
噢，感谢上帝。
I hardly have any left. My back has been killing me.
我几乎没有剩余的钱了。我的背疼得要命。
"We're sorry but your package has
“很抱歉，但您的包裹
accidentally been harmed in delivery."
在运送过程中意外受到伤害。”
I think the Post Office x-rays everything now,
我认为邮局现在会对所有东西进行X光检查，
and this looked suspicious so they opened it.
由于这看起来很可疑所以他们就打开了它。
But this is just dirt.
但这只是泥土。
Yeah, but you know Homeland Security.
是的，但是你知道国土安全部。
Man, the terrorists ruined things for everybody.
伙计，恐怖分子把大家的生活都毁了。
"Visit us at www--"
“请访问我们的网站 www--”
why do they call it visiting?
为什么他们称之为访问？
Isn't it more like "type us a letter on the computer"?
这难道不更像“在电脑上给我们一段信息”吗？
Visiting is when you go somewhere.
访问是指你去某个地方。
Yeah, you're at one place on the Internet,
是的，你在互联网上的某个地方，
and then you go someplace else.
然后你再去其他地方。
That doesn't make any sense. Yes, it does.
这毫无意义。是的，确实如此。
So if you're reading a book and you turn the page,
如果你正在读一本书，然后你翻过一页，
are you visiting another page?
您正在访问另一个页面吗？
Hold on. You still can't find your mouth
等等，你还是没找到你的嘴
without a mirror? Thank you.
没有镜子？谢谢。
Sunrise is at 6:40.
日出时间为 6:40。
You know, I put that app in your phone.
你知道，我把那个应用程序放到了你的手机里。
You don't need the almanac.
你不需要年鉴。
I like my almanac.
我喜欢我的年鉴。
What's with the mom jeans?
老妈牛仔裤（高腰牛仔裤）怎么了？
Jeans are jeans. Are you kidding?
牛仔裤就是牛仔裤。你在开玩笑吗？
Jeans mark your age more than a birth certificate.
牛仔裤比出生证明更能体现你的年龄。
Trade shoes. At least my gladiators
换鞋吧。至少我的角斗士
will get you in the right millennium.
将带你进入正确的时代。
Those are cute. Race you.
这些很可爱。跟你比赛吧。
Oh!
哦！
Took you long enough. Well, that didn't count.
花了好久。好吧，那不算数。
These aren't my shoes. Excuses, excuses.
这不是我的鞋。借口，借口。
Oh, for goodness' sake.
噢，看在上帝的份上。
What time does your class end? 9:30.
你的课什么时候结束？9:30。
Okay, then I'll meet you at work.
好的，那我在工作的地方见你。
Oh, God. Where are you going?
哦天啊。你要去哪儿？
Come back here.
回到这儿来。
Goody!
太好了！
Cradle of Filth, Ozzy Osbourne, The Cure--
Cradle of Filth、奥兹·奥斯本、The Cure——
Ooh, where?
噢，在哪里？
Oh, no. It's one of those daytime festival things.
哦，不。这是白天举行的节日活动之一。
Whose idiot idea was it
这是谁的蠢主意
to have rock concerts during the day?
白天举办摇滚音乐会？
Mmm. Let's check the traps.
嗯嗯。我们去检查一下陷阱吧。
Ugh, rats will eat anything.
呃，老鼠什么都吃。
Oh, dead one.
噢，死了一个。
Oh, trap got him?
哦，陷阱抓住他了？
I think the artificial sweeteners gave him cancer.
我认为人工甜味剂导致了他癌症。
53rd Street.
第 53 街。
And 6th Avenue.
还有第六大道。
53rd Street and 6th Avenue.
第 53 街和第六大道。
Penthouse suite.
顶层套房。
We're being summoned.
我们被传唤了。
Ask me questions. Who's the stupidest person on TV?
问我问题。电视上最蠢的人是谁？
Uh, Snooki! Oh, yes. You're right.
呃，Snooki！哦，是的。你说得对。
53rd Street.
第 53 街。
Who's the smartest?
谁最聪明？
Um, House or Frylock? Who?
呃，豪斯还是弗莱洛克？谁？
The limping doctor or the flying French fry.
跛脚的医生或飞翔的炸薯条。
53rd Street.
第 53 街。
Okay, 53rd Street.
好的，第 53 街。
Don't you love Times Square?
你不喜欢时代广场吗？
It feels like the center of the world.
感觉就像是世界的中心。
I feel like a bunch of TVs threw up.
我感觉就像一堆电视吐了一样。
Take a cab. What are you, walking?
打车吧。你在走路吗？
Okay, okay. We're coming.
好的，好的。我们来了。
What kind of mood is she in?
她心情怎样？
I've seen worse. Has she finished feeding?
我见过更糟糕的。她吃完奶了吗？
Because we don't want to be around any of that.
因为我们不想遇到这些事情。
Where are my offshoots?
我的分支在哪里？
There they are.
就在那儿。
Look at the new fall line.
看看新的秋季系列。
Gaultier, Prada.
高缇耶、普拉达。
Dress.
洋装
And I can never see how I look in them.
我永远也看不出来自己在里面是什么样子。
What is the point of looking like this
这样有什么意义
if I can never enjoy it?
如果我永远都不能享受它？
Hmm?
唔？
Oh, sucks hard. Not so nice.
噢，太糟糕了。不太好。
So put them on and then I will just imagine
穿上然后我就会想象
how much better they will look on me.
我穿起来会好看多少。
Ivan, call Mr. Pizza Guy.
伊万，打电话给披萨小哥。
I thought we were going out.
我以为我们要出去。
I feel like a pizza guy.
我感觉自己就像一个披萨小哥。
Oh, come on. Those clothes are wearing you.
哦，得了吧。这些衣服都穿在你身上了。
Give it some juice.
给它一些猛料。
I don't know about this one. Why not?
我不知道这个。为什么不呢？
It's just not for young people.
它不适合年轻人。
Excuse me?
打扰一下？
Are you telling me about being young?
你是在跟我讲年轻吗？
Do you have any idea
你知道吗
how long I have been young?
我已经年轻多久了？
She just means that, with the recession and all,
她只是想说，考虑到经济衰退等等，
girls of a certain age couldn't afford something like this.
某个年龄段的女孩买不起这样的东西。
Plus, it's fur. It's like wearing a dead animal.
而且它是皮草，穿起来就像是穿着一头死去的动物一样。
Okay, here's the flaw in that argument.
好吧，这就是该论点的缺陷。
Why should the life of a mink
水貂的生命
be more valuable than the life of a pigeon?
比鸽子的生命更有价值吗？
You two drink pigeons every day.
你们俩每天都喝鸽子酒。
We set them free.
我放了它们。
Stacy got attached. To pigeons?
Stacy对鸽子产生了感情。
You know what? We never should've named them.
你知道吗？我们根本不应该给他们起名字。
I know, you're so right.
我知道，你说得太对了。
I mean, how can you hurt something named Snuggles?
我的意思是，你怎么能伤害一个叫 Snuggles 的东西呢？
Or Mr. Doodles? Do you remember--
或者涂鸦先生？你还记得吗——
You're pathetic.
你真可怜。
Pizza guy.
披萨小子。
Who ordered the double cheese and sausage?
谁点了双层奶酪和香肠？
You're late.
你迟到了。
They said 20 minutes or less.
他们说20分钟或者更少。
You kept me waiting, you bad boy.
你让我久等了，你这个坏小子。
Sorry.
对不起。
You know what happens to bad boys.
你知道坏男孩的下场是什么。
I hate when she's in town.
我讨厌她进城。
It's disgusting. I know.
这太恶心了，我知道。
But let's just have a good time.
但让我们玩得开心点吧。
- Come on, we deserve it. - Taxi!
- 来吧，这是我们应得的。 - 出租车！
Besides, it's goth night.
此外，这是哥特之夜。
And all the day players always dress up so cute.
而且整天球员都打扮得非常可爱。
We're the oldest ones here.
我们是这里最年长的人。
Except for this schmohawk.
除了这个莫霍克发型。
Can I buy you ladies a drink? We never drink...
我可以请你们喝一杯吗？我们从不喝酒……
mojitos.
莫吉托。
Maybe you should court someone your own age.
也许你应该追求一个和你同龄的人。
Oh, did you see that cute one? Mm-hmm.
哦，你看到那只可爱的小家伙了吗？嗯嗯。
Hey. Hey, Renfield.
嘿。嘿，Renfield。
Adam Ant called. He wants his makeup back.
亚当·安特打来电话。他想要回他的化妆品。
Oh, come on. Awaken me. I wanna live forever.
噢，来吧。叫醒我。我想要永生。
Then you should try eating more broccoli.
那么你应该尝试多吃西兰花。
No, I don't want to eat more broccoli. I want to be undead.
不，我不想再吃西兰花了。我想成为不死族。
You are undead. You're alive.
你不是死人，但你还活着。
Yeah, stop imagining crazy ideas.
是的，别再想象疯狂的想法了。
No.
不。
What? Stuck-up McVainypants is here.
什么？傲慢的 McVainypants 来了。
So what? Just ignore him.
那又怎么样？别理他。
Show him how much fun you're having.
让他看看你玩得有多开心。
What? No! No pictures.
什么？不！没有照片。
Wh-- then take me.
那——那就带我去吧。
Come on. Let's just go dance.
来吧，我们去跳舞吧。
Isn't this place a little Mickey Mouse for you?
这个地方对你来说难道不就是一个小米老鼠吗？
There is Donor Club in Chinatown.
唐人街有捐助者俱乐部。
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道你在说什么。
I think I can sense a real vampire.
我想我能感觉到真正的吸血鬼。
Vampire? That word is so cornball.
吸血鬼？这个词太俗气了。
And anyone who says "cornball"
任何说“老套”的人
is at least 80 years old.
至少有80岁了。
Okay. I just don't appreciate
好吧。我只是不喜欢
being called the V-word.
被V开头的词叫。
You prefer ELF?
您更喜欢 ELF 吗？
Extended Life Form, yes.
延长生命形式，是的。
So gay.
太同性恋了。
Hey. Hi, Ivan.
嘿。嗨伊万。
I see you met Vadim. You know he's my stem.
我看你见过瓦迪姆。你知道他是我的家长。
Oh, you're the Soviet stem.
哦，你是苏联家长。
Ukrainian.
乌克兰。
Let's go to that club. Blood Bank.
我们去那个俱乐部吧。血库。
We don't feed off of people.
我们不靠人类生存。
Oh, great.
噢，太好了。
As long as Cisserus takes care of herself.
只要Cisserus照顾好自己。
Why? Anything happens to her,
为什么？她发生什么事？
your years will accrue.
你的年龄会增长。
You wouldn't want
你不会想要
to look your age.
看看你的年纪
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
I am Vadim. This is Ivan.
我是瓦迪姆。这是伊万。
I'll get my coat.
我去拿我的外套。
Oh, Juicy. She is asking for it.
哦，Juicy。这是她自找的。
Yeah, I'd say so.
是的，我会这么说。
Listen to me.
听我说。
Vadim and Ivan are bad guys.
瓦迪姆和伊万是坏人。
I like bad guys.
我喜欢坏人。
No, you like nice guys.
不，你喜欢好男人。
Don't look at them and don't talk to them.
不要看他们，不要和他们说话。
Don't talk to them.
不要和他们说话。
And remember, nice guys.
记住，好男人人。
Nice guys.
好男人。
Guys that listen when you say stuff.
当你说话时会倾听的人。
Guys that compliment you.
赞美的人。
Hey, Juicy. Where are you going?
嘿，Juicy。你要去哪里？
- Hey. We're gonna go. - BRB.
- 嘿，我们要走了。 —刚到。
Um, that only works if you're leaving.
嗯，只有当你离开时这才有效。
"Be right back."
“马上回来。”
Oh. SL. What?
哦。SL。什么？
"So long"? Close enough.
“再见”？差不多了。
So I tell my parents I'm coming to the city for my music.
所以我告诉父母我要来这座城市从事音乐。
And they say okay, as long as I go to NYU.
他们说好的，只要我能去纽约大学。
You want?
你想要吗？
No thanks. I'm already in the mood.
不用了，我已经进入状态了。
So now they're all, "What about law school?"
所以现在他们都问：“那法学院怎么样？”
And I go, "I told you I was coming here for my music."
我说：“我告诉过你我来这里是为了我的音乐。”
So they're, "Then why did we spend $100,000, Derek?"
所以他们问，“那我们为什么要花10万美元呢，德里克？”
I'm like, "You got me. You could've just gotten me
我说，“你难住我了。你刚刚难住我了
Pro Tools and I'd be happy. Law school is your dream,
专业并且我会很开心。法学院是你的梦想，
not mine."
“不是我的。”
And they think it's all about record deals,
他们认为这一切都是为了唱片合约，
but it's so different now. They're so old-fashioned.
但现在情况大不相同了。他们太守旧了。
They just don't get it, you know?
他们只是不明白，你知道吗？
Hey, my parents believed in witches.
嘿，我的父母相信女巫。
Hold on, I gotta play you something.
等一下，我得给你播放一段曲子。
Mm.
嗯。
You've got-- you've got something.
你已经得到了-- 你已经得到了一些东西。
Hmm? You want a rail?
嗯？你想要来一点么？
A little bit won't hurt.
一点点不会有事。
I gotta get out of here.
我得离开这里。
Hey, people can see you.
嘿，人们会看到你。
What? Nobody cares.
什么？没人关心。
Besides, the streets are wet and my shoes are suede.
此外，街道很湿，我的鞋是绒面革的。
Stacy, I kinda did something bad.
Stacy，我做了一些坏事。
What? Well, this drummer guy
什么？嗯，一个鼓手
was all coked up and his nose started bleeding.
他吸了可卡因，鼻子开始流血。
- Oh, no. - I just licked a drop.
- 哦，不。 - 我只是舔了一滴。
And what now? Are you jonesing? Do you have the hunger?
那现在怎么办？你渴望吗？你有饥饿感吗？
No.
不。
I just had what came out. It wasn't even flowing.
我刚刚得到了出来的东西。 它甚至不流动。
But I know it would be so much more satisfying than this whole
但我知道这会比整个
get-dressed-go-out- and-have-sex routine.
穿好衣服-出门-发生性关系的日常生活。
I mean, guys used to want to sing
我的意思是，以前男人们都想唱歌
or paint or write.
或绘画或写作。
Now, it's like iPod hits and webisodes.
现在，它就像 iPod 热播剧和网络剧一样。
Half the time, I don't even know what they're talking about.
有一半的时间我甚至不知道他们在谈论什么。
Well, we're going to group tomorrow. That always helps.
好吧，我们明天要分组。这总是有帮助的。
Hey.
嘿。
Didn't that used to be a yogurt place?
那以前不是一家酸奶店吗？
Things keep changing around here.
这里的情况不断发生变化。
Well, in the '70s, it was a methadone clinic
在 70 年代，它是一家美沙酮诊所
and all the hippies would be sitting on the stairs
所有的嬉皮士都会坐在楼梯上
waiting for their medicine.
等待他们的药。
And in the '50s, it was a dance studio,
在 50 年代，它是一家舞蹈工作室，
and everyone came to the Village to be beatniks.
每个人都来到村子里成为垮掉的一代。
And before that, it was a German newspaper.
在此之前，它是一份德国报纸。
How do you know this stuff?
你怎么知道这些的？
The History Channel. Oh.
历史频道。哦。
Uh-oh, birds.
哎呀，鸟。
Hurry. Go, go! Whoops!
快走！快走！哎呀！
Get back. Watch out, Kenny!
回去吧。小心，肯尼！
Oh!
哦！
That's Van Helsing. Let him through.
那是范海辛。让他过去。
Oh, no, no, no. This doesn't have
哦，不，不，不。这没有
anything to do with Homeland Security
任何与国土安全有关的事情
so get away from my crime scene, huh?
所以离我的犯罪现场远点，嗯？
Did you recover the neck?
脖子恢复了吗？
Look, it's your garden variety John Doe.
瞧，这就是你常说的 John Doe。
Killed, bled out someplace else,
在别处被杀，流血，
they hacked it up and dumped it here.
他们把它砍碎并扔在这里。
You call this bled out? It's bone dry.
你把这叫做流血？它已经干透了。
Detective.
侦探。
Excuse me, ma'am. I need you to back up, please.
不好意思，女士。请您后退一下。
What is that, a pizza carrier?
那是什么？披萨托盘吗？
There. You happy now?
好了。你现在开心了吗？
Hey, if we find a subway map and explosives, we'll call you.
嘿，如果我们发现地铁地图和爆炸物，我们会打电话给你。
Whoa.
哇哦。
Good evening. My name is Harry,
晚上好。我叫哈利，
and welcome to Sanguines Anonymous.
欢迎来到 Sanguines Anonymous。
Tepish, you're a stem, aren't you?
Tepish，你是一个家长，不是吗？
Someone told me that if a stem dies,
有人告诉我，如果家长死了，
all the offshoots die.
所有分支均会死亡。
It's an old wives' tale, right?
这只是一个老太太的故事吧？
I thought as long as you stayed out of the sun, you're okay.
我以为只要你不晒太阳就没事。
And if your stem died, you start aging.
如果你的家长死了，你就会开始衰老。
No, you start aging, but not like the day players.
不，你开始衰老，但不像普通人那样。
You become your chronological age.
你会成为与你实际年龄相符的人。
When were you awakened?
你是什么时间被唤醒的？
1841.
1841年。
Ah, pfft. Baby.
啊，噗。宝贝。
Besides, 200 is the new 80.
此外，200 就是新的 80。
Stacy turned in 1992.
Stacy 于 1992 年被唤醒。
Does she know how old you are?
她知道你多大了吗？
No.
不。
It seemed to comfort her thinking we were the same age.
她觉得我们年龄相同，这让她感到安慰。
Ah, I see.
啊，我明白了。
You're from Cisserus, huh? You know her?
你来自西塞罗斯，嗯？你认识她吗？
We had a fling.
我们有过一段恋情。
Mm.
嗯。
That took about a century off my life.
这让我的寿命缩短了约一个世纪。
Hey.
嘿。
Tepish, would you like to start off tonight?
特皮什，你想今晚就开始吗？
Okay.
好的。
Thank you, Harry.
谢谢你，哈利。
Hi, everyone.
大家好。
I am Vlad Tepish.
我是 Vlad Tepish。
You know, Vlad the Impaler.
您知道的，穿刺王弗拉德。
Hi, Vlad Tepish.
嗨，Vlad Tepish。
I have abstained from the fluids of homo sapiens
我戒掉人类的血液
for 362 years.
已有 362 年。
I'm sure that you've heard about what I did
我相信你已经听说了我所做的事情
to the Turkish army, huh?
土耳其军队吧？
He impaled them.
把他们刺穿了。
You youngsters have to learn how to substitute
你们年轻人必须学会如何替代
what you can't do with things that are less harmful.
用危害较小的东西来替代那些你们不能做的事。
Personally, I like knitting.
就我个人而言，我喜欢编织。
Especially...
尤其...
this part.
这部分。
Thank you, thank you. Thank you.
谢谢，谢谢，谢谢。
Hi, I'm Stacy. Hi, Stacy.
嗨，我是Stacy。嗨，Stacy。
I've been in my 20s for two decades,
我已经二十多岁了，
and when I was a day player, I was doing a lot of E.
当我还是一名普通人时，我做了很多 E 事情。
E? I don't know what that is.
E？我不知道那是什么。
That's ecstasy.
药物。
And then one night, I must've been pretty stoned,
然后有一天晚上，我肯定是嗑药了，
'cause I don't even remember,
因为我根本不记得，
but I know Cisserus was feeding on me,
但我知道Cisserus正在吸食我，
and Goody was arguing that I would be a good
Goody说我会成为一个好
clothing model for her.
的服装模特。
So if it wasn't for Goody, I would be dead.
所以如果没有Goody，我就会死。
Like, dead-dead.
就像死了一样。
But she says that I saved her because she'd been so lonely,
但她说我​​救了她，因为她太孤独了，
and having a friend made her want to keep existing.
而拥有一个朋友使得她想要继续活下去。
Even though I've never had human blood,
尽管从未吸过人类的血液，
I still feel tempted.
我仍感到心动。
But it's like drugs.
但它就像毒品一样。
We don't need the high-highs.
我们不需要高高在上。
It's more satisfying to not hurt anybody
不伤害别人使自己满足
and just have fun with your friends.
和朋友们一起享受乐趣吧。
- Thanks. - Good meeting, people.
- 谢谢。 - 很高兴见到大家。
Shall we?
我们可以？
When it comes to drinking human blood,
说到喝人血，
a single drop is too much,
一滴就太多了，
and a whole family is never enough.
而整个家庭都永远不够。
Support your fellow ELFs.
支持你的 ELF 同胞。
Undead is not unfeeling.
不死者并不是无情、
Great.
伟大的。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Don't you hate it when you sprout fangs,
你长出尖牙的时候难道不讨厌吗？
part's white and then the other part's dingy?
一部分是白色的，而另一部分却是肮脏的？
I never thought about it.
我从来没想过这件事。
It's Renfield.
是Renfield。
Hey, Renfield! Where are you guys?
嘿，Renfield！你们在哪儿？
Let's go to SoHo House.
我们去SoHo House吧。
I'm sick of these clip joints.
我厌倦了这些夹子店(脱衣舞俱乐部或夜总会)。
How about this? You go, and if it's great, text us.
这个怎么样？你去吧，如果觉得不错的话，给我们发短信。
All right. G2G.
好的。G2G。
G2G.
政府对政府。
"Got to go."
“我得走了。”
Why can't kids say entire words?
为什么孩子不能说出完整的单词？
It takes just as long to say letters.
读出字母也需要同样长的时间。
Remember, we said that we'd keep up with the times
记住，我们说过我们会与时俱进
even though it's not as good as the '80s.
尽管它不如80年代那么好。
You don't hear me complaining every time
你不会每次都听到我抱怨
a new song comes on that Devo is much better.
Devo 的新歌好听多了。
That's true.
这是真的。
You have a glob.
你有一个球体。
Here? Other side.
这里？另一边。
Here? A little higher.
这里？稍微高一点。
Doesn't it drive you crazy
这难道不会让你发疯吗
not knowing what you look like?
不知道你长什么样？
You look the same as you always did.
您看上去和往常一样。
You have pictures from before. No.
你有以前的照片。没有。
You don't have any pictures from your early years?
你没有早年的照片吗？
No.
不。
A guy in the park drew this.
这是公园里的一个男人画的。
Do I look anything like this?
我看起来像这样吗？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
He really captured you. Oh.
他确实俘获了你。噢。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Okay, she sort of has your structure.
好的，她有点了解你的结构。
You have rounder eyes,
你的眼睛更圆，
shorter chin,
下巴较短，
change the hair,
改变发型，
green eyes,
绿色的眼睛，
and...
和...
fix the nose.
修复鼻子。
And print.
并打印。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
That's me. Yeah.
那就是我。是的。
It's been so long.
已经过去好久了。
I take back everything bad I ever said about computers.
我收回我曾经说过的所有有关计算机的坏话。
Thank you. You're welcome.
谢谢。别客气。
Ooh.
哦。
Good morning. Morning.
早上好。早上好。
Ew.
那个。
Well, LASIK has come a long way.
嗯，LASIK 已经取得了长足的进步。
Hi, I'm Joey. Hi, I'm Stacy.
嗨，我是乔伊。嗨，我是Stacy。
Hey, would you like to have lunch with me sometime?
嘿，你愿意和我一起吃午饭吗？
No. Okay.
不，好的。
Um, no, what I meant was I work during the day
嗯，不，我的意思是我白天工作
but I could have coffee or drinks.
但我可以喝咖啡或饮料。
Okay, great.
好的，太好了。
All right, any questions?
好的，还有问题吗？
Yes, Professor Quincy.
是的，昆西教授。
How many surrealists does it take to change a light bulb?
换一个灯泡需要多少个超现实主义者？
How many? A bicycle.
多少？一辆自行车。
Well, thank you for that wonderful insight, Mr. Van Helsing.
好吧，谢谢您如此精彩的见解，范海辛先生。
All right, I know that was no "Talladega Nights."
好吧，我知道那不是“塔拉迪加之夜”。
Now what was Dalí trying to do in this?
那么达利这么做到底想做什么呢？
Stacy, don't take a nap.
Stacy，别睡觉。
You'll be up all day.
你会整天不眠。
I'm so tired. I was IM'ing all day.
我太累了。我整天都在发即时通讯。
I barely slept.
我几乎没睡觉。
I met someone at school.
我在学校遇见了一个人。
What's his story? He's silly.
他有什么故事？他很傻。
Goofy but cute.
傻乎乎但很可爱。
What's his name? His name?
他叫什么名字？他叫什么名字？
Um, his name is Joey...
嗯，他的名字叫乔伊......
Van Helsing.
范海辛。
What?
什么？
I'm sure it's a coincidence. It's a common name.
我确信这只是巧合。这是一个很常见的名字。
And you didn't hit it off with Timmy Hitler?
你和蒂米·希特勒合不来吗？
Very funny.
很搞笑。
I don't like it.
我不喜欢它。
I can take care of myself.
我能照顾好自己。
Guess what Joey wants to do this weekend?
猜猜乔伊这个周末想做什么？
Behead you? Ha-ha.
砍你头？哈哈。
I need to see my wife's chart.
我需要看一下我妻子的病历。
You know, I've asked about four times in the past hour.
你知道，在过去的一个小时里我问过大约四次。
So get me the goddamn chart.
所以请把那张该死的图表给我。
And don't start with the shifts.
不要从转变开始。
And you won't be sued for malpractice
你也不会因渎职而被起诉
if you do it now.
如果你现在就这么做。
Hell no, we won't go.
不行，我们不会去。
Hell no--
绝对不行——
Enough already. I've had enough.
够了。我受够了。
Hi, honey. Hi, honey.
嗨，亲爱的。嗨，亲爱的。
Love you.
爱你。
I told them not to bring you any-- look at this.
我告诉他们不要给你带任何——看看这个。
I don't want you to eat this. Look at this.
我不想让你吃这个。看看这个。
They use this for breast implants in the other wing.
他们用它在另一个房间进行隆胸手术。
Guess where I went? Cappuccino.
猜猜我去哪儿了？卡布奇诺。
Oh-- Look at this.
哦——看看这个。
How much? How much do we love cannoli?
多少钱？我们有多爱奶油甜馅煎饼卷？
All right, maybe later.
好吧，或许以后吧。
How you doing in there?
你在那儿还好吗？
Ugh.
啊。
I'm tired. Oh, shit.
我累了。哦，该死。
You got jury duty. What?
你有陪审义务。什么？
8:00 a.m. No.
上午 8:00 没有。
How could this happen?
怎么会发生这种事？
We're paid in cash. We don't do taxes.
我们以现金支付工资。我们不缴税。
I don't even have a driver's license.
我甚至没有驾照。
Our credit cards are through a third party.
我们的信用卡是通过第三方获得的。
Oh. I voted once.
哦。我投过一次票。
You what? I voted for Dukakis.
你什么？我投票给杜卡基斯。
Dukakis? It was before I turned.
杜卡基斯？在我转身之前。
And I was just thinking about the good of the country.
我只是想着国家的利益。
Country? It's just business.
国家？这只是生意而已。
From the Dutch West India Company
来自荷兰西印度公司
to the slave trade.
奴隶贸易。
How do you know all this stuff?
你怎么知道这些事的？
Um, The History Channel.
嗯，历史频道。
Yay!
耶！
If you're here and he's there, why don't you talk?
如果你在这里而他在那里，为什么不说话呢？
Nobody talks.
没人说话。
Do you want him to think I'm 40?
你想让他以为我 40 岁了吗？
So, if the city has too much garbage,
所以，如果城市垃圾太多，
and rats eat garbage,
老鼠吃垃圾，
why don't we just get rats to eat the garbage
我们为什么不让老鼠吃垃圾呢
instead of spraying toxic crap everywhere?
而不是随处喷洒有毒物质？
Rats breed too quickly. So?
老鼠繁殖得太快了。那么呢？
What if we give them birth control?
如果我们给予他们避孕措施会怎么样？
You mean get rats to put on condoms?
你的意思是让老鼠戴上避孕套？
Yeah. Teensy-weensy little condoms.
是的。超小的避孕套。
Who's that old hippie talking to Fred?
和弗雷德说话的那个老嬉皮士是谁？
You must mean the girls from the graveyard shift.
你肯定是指那些上夜班的女孩。
Shit. I used to go out with him
妈的。我以前和他约会过
before you and I knew each other.
在我和你互相认识之前。
Oh, my God. He's gonna expect you to be like 40.
哦天哪。他以为你会是 40 岁左右。
I know. Hi.
我知道。嗨。
Wow.
哇。
How is it possible?
这怎么可能呢？
Goody, you have not aged a day.
好极了，你一点都没老。
Mister, my name is Susan.
先生，我叫苏珊。
But my mother's name was Goody. Did you know her?
但我妈妈的名字叫Goody。你认识她吗？
Goody Rutherford? Is that your mother?
好人卢瑟福？那是你妈妈吗？
Yes, but she passed away.
是的，但是她已经去世了。
Oh. I-I-I'm sorry.
哦。我很抱歉。
My name is Danny Horowitz.
我叫丹尼霍洛维茨。
Did she ever, uh, you know, like, mention me?
她有没有提过我？
I think.
我认为。
But we have to get to work. Hey.
但我们得开始工作了。嘿。
Hi, I under-- listen. I have to talk to you.
嗨，我明白了。我有事要跟你谈谈。
Please call me tomorrow.
请明天给我打电话。
Okay. Tomorrow night.
好的。明天晚上。
Night, of course.
当然是晚上了。
Just like your mother.
就像你的母亲一样。
Okay.
好的。
So, is this your place? It's my parents' place.
那么，这是你的家吗？这是我父母的家。
When my ex and I broke up, I was traveling
当我和前任分手时，我正在旅行
and I haven't found a new place yet.
我还没找到新住处。
Iris recognition. So, what does your dad do?
虹膜识别。那么，你的爸爸是做什么的呢？
Well, he works for Homeland Security now,
嗯，他现在在国土安全部工作，
but he was with MI-6 in London for quite a long time.
但他在伦敦的军情六处工作了很长一段时间。
So is he, um, some kind of spy?
那么他是某种间谍吗？
Yeah, like James Bond but shorter.
是的，像詹姆斯邦德，但是个子更矮。
Listen, Stacy. There's something I have to tell you.
听着，Stacy。我有件事要告诉你。
What? I'm older than you think.
什么？我比你想象的还要老。
I've been helping my dad with this project for a few years,
我已经帮助我爸爸做这个项目几年了，
and since I'm still in school, you probably think I'm, like, 20.
由于我还在上学，所以你可能认为我大概 20 岁。
But I'm almost 25.
但我快25岁了。
And since you're like 17--
因为你才17岁——
Um, actually I'm a little bit older
嗯，实际上我年纪稍大一些
than the other kids, too.
比其他孩子更
You are?
你是？
Well, great. Well, how old are you?
嗯，太好了。那么，你多大了？
You don't ask a lady her age.
你不会询问女士的年龄。
Well, why not? Because it's very impolite.
那为什么不呢？因为这很不礼貌。
How am I gonna find out? I don't know.
我怎么才能知道呢？我不知道。
I'm gonna nick your passport.
我要偷走你的护照。
I'm never going again. The performance was ghastly.
我再也不会去了。表演太糟糕了。
No, the clown was so--
不，小丑是如此——
Joey. Oh.
乔伊。哦。
I didn't know you had company.
我不知道你还有同伴。
We just got back. This is Stacy.
我们刚回来。我是Stacy。
Stacy, my mother and father.
Stacy，我的父母。
Hi, Stacy. Oh, pleasure.
嗨，Stacy。噢，很高兴。
Nice to meet you. Uh, yeah.
很高兴认识你。呃，是的。
How do you do? Hi.
你好吗？嗨。
Well, I actually have to get to my job.
嗯，我实际上得去上班了。
You work at night?
你晚上上班吗？
Yeah, it's so depressing.
是啊，真是令人沮丧。
But, you know, just until school gets out.
但你知道，直到放学为止。
I have to go. I'll see you out.
我得走了。我送你出去。
Ta! Yeah.
太棒了！是的。
Did you feel her hands? Freezing.
你感觉到她的手了吗？好冷。
I'm glad you're interested. Are you a registered voter?
我很高兴你感兴趣。你是登记选民吗？
No matter what's going on in the world,
不管世间发生什么，
there's always someone protesting or petitioning,
总有人抗议或请愿，
and they always wind up in Union Square.
他们总是会聚集在联合广场。
Even in the 1840s, people were pamphleteering for abolition.
甚至到了 19 世纪 40 年代，人们就在散发宣传册，呼吁废除奴隶制。
...southern flesh peddlers!
...南方的肉贩子！
Slavery will tear our country apart!
奴隶制将会撕裂我们的国家！
Sir, may I proffer you a pamphlet?
先生，我可以给您提供一本小册子吗？
Abolition now!
立即废除！
Sir-- sir, may I proffer you a pamphlet?
先生——先生，我可以给您提供一本小册子吗？
And in the 1950s,
20 世纪 50 年代，
thousands of people protested to stop
数千人抗议阻止
the execution of the Rosenbergs.
罗森堡夫妇被处决。
Of course, in the '60s, there was always a Vietnam demonstration.
当然，在 60 年代，一直都有越南示威活动。
Hell no, we won't go!
不行，我们才不去！
Hell no, we won't go! Hell no...
不行，我们才不去！不行……
Must've been pretty crazy to see your old boyfriend like that, huh?
看到前男友这样，你一定很疯狂，是吧？
How long were you guys together?
你们在一起多久了？
Over a year. We never lived together,
一年多。我们从未同居过，
but we saw each other every night.
但我们每天晚上都会见面。
I forgot how nice it felt seeing someone you love all the time.
我忘了时常见到自己爱的人那种感觉有多么美好。
I wonder what Joey's parents think about me.
我想知道乔伊的父母对我有何看法。
So what did you think of Stacy?
那么您觉得 Stacy 怎么样？
She's rather pale.
她的脸色相当苍白。
How do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
What your mother means is she's...
你妈妈的意思是她...
exceedingly white.
非常白。
So you don't like her because of the color of her skin?
所以你不喜欢她是因为她的肤色吗？
Is that what you're telling me?
这就是你要告诉我的吗？
Oh, don't be so dramatic.
噢，别这么戏剧化。
No, it's simply that she's not like us.
不，只是她和我们不一样。
You mean wealthy, over-educated,
你指的是富裕、受过高等教育的人，
Upper-West-Side, paranoid, ghoul-chasing--
上西区，偏执狂，追杀鬼魂——
Oh, for fuck's sake. She's undead!
哦，妈的，她还没死！
And I forbid you to see her!
我禁止你见她！
You think everyone is a vampire.
你认为每个人都是吸血鬼。
Just because somebody stays up late,
只是因为有人熬夜，
doesn't go to bed before 3:00...
3点之前不睡觉...
Well excuse me for being overly vigilant.
好吧，请原谅我过于警惕。
...doesn't mean hey can just grow fangs,
...这并不意味着他们就能长出尖牙，
put on a black cape... But I think beings
披上黑色斗篷……但我认为
devoid of warm blood... ...and fly around tow like a bat!
没有温血......像蝙蝠一样飞来飞去！
Just because they're a little peaky,
只是因为它们有点尖，
it doesn't mean they drink blood.
这并不意味着他们喝血。
...roam the street at night looking for innocent victims.
...晚上在街上游荡寻找无辜的受害者。
You are so intolerant.
你太不宽容了。
Enough! Stop it, both of you.
够了！你们两个都别再这样了。
Let's just invite your little friend to supper.
我们就邀请你的小朋友来吃晚饭吧。
If she's one of them, we'll know.
如果她是其中之一，我们就会知道。
Fine.
美好的。
Tonight, we're meeting under sad circumstances.
今晚，我们在悲伤的情况下相聚。
I'm sure by now you've all heard about David's
我相信现在你们都听说过大卫的
tragic Daylight Savings accident.
悲惨的夏令时事故。
Boy, one century you're here
孩子，一个世纪以来你一直在这里
and the next you're gone.
然后你就走了。
Do you sense something gross?
你感觉到有什么恶心的东西了吗？
Yes.
是的。
I see we have a newcomer.
我看到我们有一位新人。
Uh, yeah, hi. I'm Rita.
嗯，是的，你好。我是丽塔。
Hi, Rita.
嗨丽塔。
I am a psy-vampire.
我是一个精神吸血鬼。
What exactly is that? Psychic vampire.
那到底是什么？精神吸血鬼。
I'm able to feed off other people's auras.
我能够吸收其他人的气场。
You know, I absorb their energy.
你知道，我吸收了他们的能量。
How do you know you're not just annoying them?
你怎么知道你没有惹恼他们呢？
Psy-vampires are a true vampiric subset, okay?
精神吸血鬼是真正的吸血鬼子集，好吗？
And we don't need blood to draw--
我们不需要抽血来——
What the fuck is that?
那他妈是什么？
All right, all right. Settle down.
好啦好啦，冷静点。
We really gotta be more careful
我们确实要更加小心
about how we announce our meetings.
关于我们如何宣布会议。
Anybody else have something to share?
有谁还有东西可以分享吗？
Stacy got called in for jury duty,
Stacy被召去担任陪审员，
but she hasn't voted since the '80s.
但自80年代以来她就没有投票过。
That happened to me.
那件事发生在我身上。
And they're bringing me in for an audit.
他们正在带我去接受审计。
Everybody call on your stems
每个人都呼唤你的茎
and any human-feeders you know.
以及您认识的任何喂食人类的动物。
But how are we gonna find Cisserus?
但是我们怎样才能找到西塞罗斯？
You don't know her resting place?
你不知道她的安息之地吗？
When she wants us, she summons us.
当她需要我们时，她就会召唤我们。
We never call on her.
我们从不拜访她。
Okay.
好的。
We all gotta work together, folks.
大家好，我们大家都必须共同努力。
The community is being persecuted.
这个社区正在遭受迫害。
I've seen it all before.
我以前就见过这一切。
Now instead of tortures, they're using computers.
现在他们不再使用酷刑，而是使用计算机。
Does Mr. Davidoff know you are coming?
大卫杜夫先生知道您要来吗？
Mr. Davidoff is aware
大卫杜夫先生知道
we'll be here between 7:00 a.m. and 12:00 p.m.
我们将在上午 7:00 至下午 12:00 之间到达
But don't you need a search warrant?
但你不需要搜查令吗？
Madam, you've insultingly confused us with the police.
女士，您侮辱性地把我们和警察混淆了。
I'm from Time Warner,
我来自时代华纳，
and if you ever want to see Jon Stewart again,
如果你想再次见到乔恩·斯图尔特，
you'll open this door.
你会打开这扇门。
Let's get some light in here.
我们来这里找点光吧。
Morning, Sunshine.
早上好，阳光。
Buenas noches, chicas.
晚安，女孩们。
Have you seen Ivan?
你见过伊万吗？
He hasn't answered any of my summonses.
他还没有回应我的任何传票。
Uh, I think we saw him last week.
呃，我想我们上周见过他。
Something must have happened.
肯定发生什么事了。
He's not strong enough to ignore you.
他还不够强大到可以无视你。
Well, you chicas will just have to fill in.
好吧，你们这些女孩只需填写即可。
But we're only good at modeling and light clerical work.
但我们只擅长建模和轻松的文书工作。
So, you fold these carefully,
所以你小心地折叠它们，
and you pack this soil.
然后你把这片土壤压实。
Don't you just love these "As-seen-on-TV" bags?
难道您不喜欢这些“如同电视上所见”的包包吗？
Look how much soil it can fit.
看看它能容纳多少土壤。
Oh, it's a good thing we're here because there's gonna be
哦，我们来这里真好，因为
a big meeting with all the local stems and ELFs.
与所有当地 STEM 和 ELF 举办的大型会议。
There's been a lot of persecution of the community.
社区遭受了很多迫害。
What do I care? Well, if you keep acting
我关心什么？好吧，如果你继续演戏
so recklessly, they're gonna find you.
如此鲁莽，他们就会找到你。
No one will ever find my lair.
没人能找到我的巢穴。
And I'm in the one place no New Yorker ever goes.
我现在所处的地方是纽约人从来不去的地方。
But your behavior makes it harder for everyone else.
但你的行为却让其他人的日子更难过。
For who?
为了谁？
For Vlad Tepish and his doofus peasants?
为了 Vlad Tepish 和他那些愚蠢的农民？
"Vlad the Impaler"?
“穿刺王弗拉德”？
I'll tell you what that whole impaling routine was.
我会告诉你整个刺穿过程是怎样的。
Compensation.
赔偿。
You know what I'm saying?
你知道我在说什么吗？
Besides, I am leaving town.
此外，我要离开这个城镇。
And look at this pimpin' travel coffin he made me.
看看他给我做的这个旅行棺材。
Here's the itinerary.
这是行程。
Just get me on cargo before dawn.
只要在黎明前把我送上货舱就行。
It's a private jet.
这是一架私人飞机。
Spain? What's in Spain?
西班牙？西班牙有什么？
It is not just the rain in Spain.
西班牙不只是有雨。
Look at him.
看看他。
Diego Bardem.
迭戈·巴登。
Only the handsomest, most talented man in the world.
只有世界上最英俊、最有才华的男人。
Do you know him? No, I don't know him.
你认识他吗？不，我不认识他。
But I got mad love for him.
但我疯狂地爱上了他。
And I'll tell you a secret.
我会告诉你一个秘密。
I am not gonna use any hypnotism.
我不会使用任何催眠疗法。
I want this to be real.
我希望这是真的。
I haven't felt this way about anyone since Al Jolson.
自从艾尔·乔逊之后，我就没对任何人有过这种感觉。
The Mammy guy?
那个叫妈咪的家伙？
Yes, the Mammy guy.
是的，就是那个叫妈咪的家伙。
I mean, he was an amazingly dynamic performer.
我的意思是，他是一位极其有活力的表演者。
You have no idea because you never saw him live.
你不知道，因为你从未亲眼见过他。
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
哦哦哦哦哦
Hey.
嘿。
What did your parents say about me?
你的父母是怎么说我的？
Are you near your computer? Yeah.
你在电脑旁边吗？是的。
Come on iChat. I wanna see you.
来吧，iChat。我想见你。
Oh!
哦！
I don't-- I don't have iChat.
我没——我没有 iChat。
Yeah, you do. It's built in.
是的，确实如此。它是内置的。
Yeah, but my roommate was spray painting
是的，但我的室友正在喷漆
and she got paint on the lens.
她的镜头上沾上了油漆。
So... Pfft.
所以……噗。
What did your parents say?
你的父母怎么说？
They thought you were a bit pale.
他们觉得你的脸色有点苍白。
What do you mean pale?
苍白是什么意思？
Well, you know, pale, fair skin.
嗯，你知道，皮肤白皙。
Like maybe you were sick or something.
就像你可能病了或者怎么了。
Well, it's just those environmental light bulbs.
嗯，只是因为那些环保灯泡。
I mean, they make everybody look horrible.
我的意思是，他们让每个人看起来都很糟糕。
Look, they want you to come for dinner on Friday.
瞧，他们想让你星期五来吃饭。
Can you make it?
你能做到吗？
Oh, I'll be there.
噢，我会去的。
Stay still.
保持静止。
It's good, right? I think it's totally working.
很好，对吧？我认为它完全有效。
I'm gonna be so tan.
我会变得黑黑的。
Hi.
你好。
Wow. You look...
哇。你看上去……
Robust?
强壮？
Sure.
当然。
Come in. Dinner will be a few minutes.
进来吧。晚餐还有几分钟就好了。
Let me give you the tour.
让我带你参观一下。
What is all this stuff?
这是什么东西？
Well, it's mostly stuff from my grandfather
嗯，大部分都是我祖父的东西
or my great grandfather.
或者我的曾祖父。
My father is an expert on vampirism.
我的父亲是吸血鬼研究专家。
Told you my family's nuts.
告诉你我家人的疯狂。
What's this thing? Ah, well...
这是什么东西？啊，好吧……
if someone you suspect of being a vampire dies,
如果你怀疑某个吸血鬼死了，
you place this over their neck before they're buried
在他们被埋葬之前，你把这个放在他们的脖子上
and if they wake up and try to climb out of their coffin,
如果他们醒来并试图爬出棺材，
they get beheaded.
就会被斩首。
Dinner's ready!
晚餐准备好了！
Hey, I know him.
嘿，我认识他。
You know him?
你认识他吗？
I mean, I know who he is.
我的意思是，我知道他是谁。
It's Vlad Tepish.
这是 Vlad Tepish。
It's pronounced "Tee-pees."
它的发音为“Tee-pees”。
He was one of the most sadistic figures in history.
他是历史上最残暴的人物之一。
Well, I guess that sort of depends on your point of view.
嗯，我想这取决于你的观点。
Really?
真的吗？
How many points of view can there be on the subject
关于这个问题可以有多少种观点
of impaling people and drinking their blood?
刺穿人并喝他们的血？
If a weird stunt like that stops
如果这种奇怪的特技停止了
the entire Ottoman Empire from taking over Europe.
整个奥斯曼帝国占领欧洲。
His armor is in the museum in Bucharest.
他的盔甲现藏于布加勒斯特博物馆。
I mean, they consider him a hero.
我的意思是，他们认为他是一位英雄。
Yeah, if it wasn't for him, we'd all be speaking "Ottomanese."
是的，如果没有他，我们都会说“奥斯曼语”。
Didn't you like your fish?
你不喜欢吃鱼吗？
Shall we make something else for you?
我们能为您做点别的吗？
Oh, no, thank you, Mrs. Van Helsing.
哦，不，谢谢你，范海辛夫人。
I'm enjoying my dinner a great deal.
我非常享受我的晚餐。
Now, you must try our soup.
现在，您一定要尝尝我们的汤。
It's an old Van Helsing recipe.
这是范海辛 (Van Helsing) 的一个古老食谱。
Ahh!
啊啊！
Not a fan of garlic?
不喜欢大蒜吗？
Oh, no, it's not the garlic. It's the salt.
哦不，这不是大蒜的问题，是盐的问题。
Even the tiniest bit and I blow up
即使是最微小的一点，我也会爆炸
like a Thanksgiving Day balloon.
就像感恩节气球。
My father thinks that if he gives us garlic breath,
我父亲认为如果让我们嘴里有大蒜味，
we won't make out.
我们就不会亲热。
Not going to work, Pops.
不行，爸爸。
Ma, we'll take dessert later. The movie starts at 9:30.
妈，我们待会儿再吃甜点。电影 9:30 开始。
I'll just get our things.
我只是去拿我们的东西而已。
Hmm.
唔。
You have a very strong will, Dr. Van Helsing.
您的意志非常坚强，范海辛博士。
What are your intentions with my son?
你对我儿子到底有什么打算？
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
Do you plan to suck the life out of him?
你打算吸干他的生命吗？
No more than any other girlfriend.
不比其他女朋友多。
Hey, you ready?
嘿，你准备好了吗？
Thank you for dinner.
谢谢你的晚餐。
See you later.
待会儿见。
Oh, I know. But did you see the girl
哦，我知道。但是你看到那个女孩了吗？
who left with Joey? Is she one of them?
谁和 Joey 一起离开了？她是其中之一吗？
I wasn't really paying attention.
我并没注意。
That girl, she seemed pretty dark.
那个女孩，看上去挺黑的。
But it's all gonna be on my phone.
但一切都会记录在我的手机上。
So hold on.
所以坚持一下。
Wait, I don't remember seeing empty chairs.
等一下，我不记得看到过空椅子。
What did I do wrong?
我做错了什么？
You didn't do anything wrong.
你没有做错任何事。
Why do people bother going out
人们为什么要费心外出
if the only thing they want to bond with
如果他们唯一想与之建立联系的东西
is their little glowing boxes?
是发光小盒子
Don't go grandma on me.
别像奶奶一样对我。
Oh, there's Renfield. Hey.
哦，那是 Renfield。嘿。
Uh, you guys, um...
呃，你们，嗯……
kinda can't sit here unless we order a $400 bottle.
除非我们点一瓶 400 美元的酒，否则根本没法坐在这里。
- Don't worry about it. - Bottle service.
- 别担心。 - 瓶装服务(高档酒吧或夜总会的特色服务)。
She left him 10 minutes ago. The sex must be great.
她 10 分钟前就离开了他。性生活一定很棒。
Oh, we haven't done it yet.
哦，我们还没有做。
Oh, so it's a purely textual relationship?
哦，那么只是笔友？
I've been looking for you, you lifeless bitch.
我一直在找你，你这个死气沉沉的婊子。
What is your problem?
什么事？
What did you do to Ivan?
你对伊万做了什么？
What are you talking about?
你在说什么？
First you kill my game with Juicy girl.
首先，你毁了我的游戏。
Now Ivan is missing.
如今，伊万失踪了。
Suckerin' succotash.
天啊
Guys, guys, guys!
伙计们，伙计们，伙计们！
Not in front of the day players.
不要在白天的玩家面前。
The past few minutes, you remember nothing.
过去的几分钟，你什么都不记得了。
Complete Sergeant Schultz.
完成舒尔茨中士的任务。
I know nothing!
我什么都不知道！
I saw nothing! Now cut it out.
我什么也没看到！现在就停止吧。
Besides, why would we hurt Ivan?
此外，我们为什么要伤害伊万？
We'd just wind up doing more work for Cisserus.
我们最终只会为 Cisserus 做更多的工作。
Actually, it's a good thing we ran into you.
事实上，遇到你是件好事。
We need you to come to a Sanguines Anonymous meeting.
我们需要您参加 Sanguines Anonymous 会议。
No way. You don't have to join,
不。你不必加入，
but a lot of weird stuff has been going down.
但很多奇怪的事情发生了。
They're trying to force us out into the sun.
他们试图强迫我们到阳光下生活。
You think this has something to do with Ivan's disappearance?
你认为这和伊万的失踪有关吗？
It might.
有可能。
Did anyone in his building see anything?
他所在大楼里的任何人看到什么吗？
The neighbor said the cable company was there.
邻居说有线电视公司就在那里。
Can Time Warner just burst into a person's home and kill them?
时代华纳真的能闯入某人的家并杀死他们吗？
Yeah, they're terrible.
是的，他们很糟糕。
Come to a meeting. We've got to figure this out.
来开会吧。我们必须解决这个问题。
Everybody's getting audited.
每个人都要接受审计。
Well, you don't have to go.
那你不必去。
What?
什么？
An audit is just the IRS saying,
审计只是美国国税局的说法，
"We think you should pay more taxes."
“我们认为你应该缴纳更多的税。”
And if you agree with them, then you say, "Okay, how much?"
如果你同意他们，那么你就说，“好吧，多少？”
But you only have to go in if you wanna challenge them.
但只有当你想挑战他们时你才要进去。
How do you know this?
你怎么知道的？
I'm a CPA.
我是一名注册会计师。
You are? Yeah.
是吗？是的。
You just got some new clients.
您刚刚获得了一些新客户。
Not me. I have a guy.
不是我。我有一个男朋友。
What are you wearing?
你穿了什么？
It's like the history of fashion.
就像时尚的历史。
I'm going to see Danny. I wanna look nice.
我要去见丹尼。我想打扮得漂漂亮亮。
Gibson Girl shirts were the prettiest.
吉布森女孩 (Gibson Girl) 衬衫是最漂亮的。
1960s skirts are great on short women.
20 世纪 60 年代的裙子非常适合矮个子女性。
1970s shoes make you tall but are comfortable.
20 世纪 70 年代的鞋子虽然让你显得高大，但却很舒适。
Okay, but what's with the hat?
好的，但是那顶帽子是怎么回事？
It's a boater.
这是一位船夫。
People always said it looked spiffy on me.
人们总是说它在我身上很漂亮。
People from your barbershop quartet
你的理发店四重奏成员
or people from the Republican convention?
还是共和党大会的代表？
Oh, God.
哦，天啊。
Here we are.
我们到了。
"Architectural Digest" time. Enjoy yourself.
《建筑文摘》时间到了。玩得开心。
Sure you don't want anything to drink?
你确实不想喝点什么吗？
I'm sure. Well, I'm not.
我确定。嗯，我不确定。
I need some coffee, man. For energy.
哥们，我需要喝点咖啡来补充能量。
I just made this last week.
我上周刚刚做了这个。
Oh. You work for the government?
哦。你在政府工作吗？
Do I look like I work for the government?
我看起来像是政府工作人员吗？
I'm with the ACLU.
我是美国公民自由联盟的成员。
Right now I'm in the middle of this deportation case
现在我正处于驱逐出境案件之中
with abuses of wiretapping. It's unbearable.
滥用电话窃听。这让人无法忍受。
Well, I thought if the government
嗯，我想如果政府
doesn't hear terrorist-related stuff,
不听与恐怖主义有关的事情，
they have to hang up.
他们需要挂断电话。
No.
不。
Ah, look at this.
啊，看看这个。
I was going through these looking for your mother.
我正在通过这些来寻找你的母亲。
Look at these.
看看这些。
She had this habit of just
她有这样的习惯
ducking out right before they took a picture.
在拍照之前就躲开了。
Well, she was superstitious.
嗯，她很迷信。
Still, I mean, it's a little nutty, isn't it?
不过，我的意思是，这有点疯狂，不是吗？
My God.
我的上帝。
I have this one. You do? Really?
我有这个。你有吗？真的吗？
She saved it?
她救了它吗？
You better put yours in plastic.
你最好把它放在塑料袋里。
She liked this, huh? Well, why not?
她喜欢这个，是吧？那又有什么不好呢？
I was not bad-looking back then, huh?
我那时候长得还不错吧？
What an amazing time this was.
这是多么奇妙的时光啊。
Being young and in love.
年轻且在恋爱中。
Feeling like you're a part of something that really mattered.
感觉自己是某个真正重要的事情的一部分。
Your mother never mentioned why she just disappeared?
你母亲从来没提过她为什么就消失了？
Not really. Oh, man.
不是的。哦天啊。
Hey, you know what?
嘿，你知道吗？
I have to get movies for my wife before the store closes.
我必须在商店关门前给我妻子买电影。
Right on. Huh?
没错。嗯？
My way.
我的方式。
I'll go with. Oh.
我跟你一起去。哦。
All right, cool.
好的，很酷。
You know, Angela is really in and out.
你知道，安吉拉确实时好时坏。
And that's why I gotta get her movies that she really loves.
这就是为什么我要给她看她真正喜欢的电影。
So, you know, when she dozes off,
所以，当她打瞌睡的时候，
you know, she won't miss anything, really.
你知道，她真的不会错过任何事情。
Can I help? Uh, no.
我能帮忙吗？呃，没办法。
When I see 'em, I'll know it.
当我看到它们时我就会知道。
Then I'm gonna look around. Okay, cool.
然后我要四处看看。好的，很酷。
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
Do you have any James Cagney posters?
你有詹姆斯·卡格尼的海报吗？
Oh, James Cameron?
哦，詹姆斯·卡梅隆？
No, uh, James Cagney.
不，呃，詹姆斯·卡格尼。
You know, "Made it, Ma! Top of the world!"
你知道的，“成功了，妈妈！世界之巅！”
No.
不。
What about...
那...
Fred Astaire? No.
弗雷德·阿斯坦？不。
Jack Lemmon? No.
杰克·莱蒙？不。
Paul Newman. Oh, the salad dressing guy?
保罗·纽曼。哦，那个沙拉酱小伙子？
Yeah. No.
是啊。不是。
Phones on the ground.
手机在地上。
Phones on the ground now. Drop 'em!
手机现在在地面上。扔掉它们！
Hands in the air. Hands in the air. Give me the money.
举起双手。举起双手。把钱给我。
Don't you point that. He's got a heart condition.
你别指着他。他有心脏病。
Shut up! Oh, my God!
闭嘴！天啊！
Fuck. Come on!
操，来吧！
He's having a heart attack. No, no, no, lady.
他心脏病发作了。不，不，不，女士。
Get up and give me the money now.
快起来，把钱给我。
Shit, come on! Oh!
妈的，拜托！噢！
Stop it.
停下来。
Calm down.
冷静下来。
Mm. Feel better?
嗯。感觉好些了吗？
Yeah.
是的。
You are gonna take this couple to the hospital.
你要带这对夫妇去医院。
And no more stealing.
不再偷窃。
The bite was from your cat.
被你的猫咬了。
You guys, take CPR courses.
你们，参加心肺复苏术课程。
You hate junk food.
你讨厌垃圾食品。
And get "Public Enemy."
并获得“公众之敌”。
The Cagney one.
卡格尼那个。
You all right?
你还好吗？
I could hypnotize you,
我可以催眠你，
but I've been wanting to tell you.
但我一直想告诉你。
So what are you saying? You broke up with me 'cause
那你到底想说什么？你跟我分手是因为
you wouldn't drink my blood? Is that what you're telling me?
你不会喝我的血？这就是你告诉我的吗？
I don't drink human blood.
我不喝人血。
You don't? That guy, what was that?
你不知道吗？那家伙是什么？
No. Have you ever seen a vampire bat?
不。你见过吸血蝙蝠吗？
A little rodent can get the blood out of an entire cow
由于唾液中含有酶，
in a few minutes because of this enzyme in their saliva.
一只小啮齿动物可以在几分钟内吸出一整头牛的血。
It's a completely safe blood thinner.
它是一种完全安全的血液稀释剂。
And I also have it.
我也有。
I didn't drink that man's blood.
我没有喝那人的血。
I spit into him to stop the stroke.
我朝他吐了口唾沫，让他停止中风。
Oh. You just spit into him.
哦。你就朝他吐口水吧。
Oh, that's a whole other ball game.
噢，那又是另一回事了。
Well, if I didn't, he would have had a lot of brain damage.
好吧，如果我不这么做的话，他的脑部就会受到严重损伤。
How old are you?
你今年多大？
A little older than you.
比你大一点。
So people can only be around you for, like, what--
所以人们只能在你身边待一段时间——
a year or something?
一年左右？
No, I could go around seven years
不，我可以花七年左右的时间
without them expecting me to look older.
他们并不指望我看起来会老一些。
And I would've stayed with you for as long as possible.
我会尽可能长久地陪伴你。
But when you became one of the student leaders,
但当你成为学生领袖之一时，
people on the street recognized you.
街上的人们认出了你。
I thought, "This is his time."
我想：“这是他的时代了。”
You could have your choice of any woman out there.
你可以选择那里的任何一位女人。
It didn't seem right to rob you of the chance
剥夺你遇见某个了不起的人
to meet someone amazing.
的机会似乎是不对的。
And you did, didn't you?
你确实这么做了，不是吗？
I did. I really did.
是的，我确实这么做了。
And you know what? I really should check
你知道吗？我真的应该检查一下
and see how she's doing.
看看她做得怎么样。
And I gotta tell you something else.
我还要告诉你另外一件事。
I feel like I'm really, like, tripping right now.
我感觉自己现在真的像是被绊住了一样。
Am I gonna see you again?
我还会再见到你吗？
Uh...
呃…
of course, yeah.
当然。
Okay, this is Germany before World War II.
好的，这是第二次世界大战前的德国。
The sleepwalker keeps murdering people,
梦游者不断杀人，
but only because the evil guy has him under a spell.
但这只是因为那个邪恶的家伙迷住了他。
What does that remind you of?
这让你想起了什么？
I'm flummoxed.
我困惑了。
Germany? Evil spell?
德国？邪恶咒语？
Adolf?
阿道夫？
Your eyes remind me of somebody.
你的眼睛让我想起了某个人。
Adolf Hitler.
阿道夫·希特勒。
No, that wasn't who I was thinking of.
不，我所想的并不是那个人。
Audrey Hepburn. Same initials, though.
奥黛丽赫本。不过姓名首字母相同。
Can you please just focus on symbolism?
你能只关注象征意义吗？
Sorry.
对不起。
Can I be under your spell?
我可以受你的迷惑吗？
Or better still, you could be under my spell.
或者更好的是，你可能会被我迷住。
What are you gonna make me do?
你要让我做什么？
Laugh hysterically.
狂笑。
Holy shit.
我靠。
Has it ever been like that for your before?
您以前也遇到过这样的情况吗？
Not since the '80s.
从 80 年代以来就没有了。
Hey, where are you going?
嘿，你要去哪儿？
Um, I've got an early class.
嗯，我有一节早课。
Well, ditch it and come back to bed.
好吧，别再想这件事了，回床上去。
I can't. But I'll call you later.
不行。不过我稍后会给你打电话。
Come on, my parents won't be home until tomorrow.
拜托，我父母明天才回家。
Look, it's a little early in the relationship to get into this,
听着，现在谈这个还为时过早，
but I've really gotta go.
但我真的得走了。
What the--
什么——
Something bothering you? What?
有什么事让你烦恼吗？什么？
No.
不。
If there's anything you wanna talk about...
如果您有什么想谈论的...
maybe trouble with Stacy, or...
也许是与 Stacy 有麻烦，或者...
Yeah, 'cause you'd love that.
是的，因为你会喜欢的。
He's not answering my texts, my tweets, my e-mails,
他不回复我的短信、推文、电子邮件，
my voicemail, my Facebook messages--
我的语音邮件、我的 Facebook 信息——
Do you think he'll tell his father?
你认为他会告诉他父亲吗？
No, he wouldn't do that. What about Danny?
不，他不会这么做。丹尼怎么办？
Do you think he'll tell the authorities?
你认为他会告诉当局吗？
He'd never. How do you know?
他永远不会。你怎么知道？
Danny hates authority.
丹尼讨厌权威。
I'm gonna go to his class so he has to confront me.
我要去他的课，所以他必须与我对质。
Are you mad at me?
你气死我了？
Don't go away. Huh? What?
别走。啊？啥？
Really? Yeah.
真的吗？是的。
How do you like them apples?
您喜欢这些苹果吗？
Garlic?
蒜？
You were afraid of it the other night.
那天晚上你很害怕它。
Yeah, because I've always hated garlic.
是的，因为我一直讨厌大蒜。
Can we please just talk about this?
我们可以就此展开讨论吗？
My father tried to warn me. Against what?
我父亲曾试图警告我。警告什么呢？
I have never harmed a human being or a domestic animal
我从未伤害过人类或家畜
my entire life.
我的一生。
Oh, so you didn't go after me 'cause I'm a Van Helsing?
哦，所以你没有追我，因为我是范海辛？
No. If anything, I would've stayed away.
不。如果可以的话，我就会远离。
Besides, if I wanted to drink your blood,
此外，如果我想喝你的血，
would I have written you this 10-page report
我会需要给你10页的报告？
on Freud and his influence on surrealist imagery?
关于弗洛伊德及其对超现实主义意象的影响？
How do I know you wrote this for me?
我怎么知道这是你为我写的？
Because I also wrote one on World War I
因为我也写过一篇关于第一次世界大战的文章
and how it gave birth to Surrealism.
以及它是如何催生超现实主义的。
Actually, I like that one better.
事实上，我更喜欢那个。
Oh, you do?
噢，是吗？
So now you trust me, huh?
所以现在你相信我了，是吧？
I trust you to give yourself the better grade.
我相信你会有一个更好的成绩。
I don't blame you.
我不怪你。
You know I would never hurt you, right?
你知道我永远不会伤害你，对吧？
Yeah.
是的。
Well, then what is it? Is it the day thing?
那么，那是什么呢？是白天的事吗？
Do you want to have a girlfriend
你想找个女朋友吗
you can go hiking with and go to the beach?
您可以一起去徒步旅行和去海滩吗？
No, I'm-- I'm more of a night person.
不，我——我更像是一个夜猫子。
Is it the blood, then?
那么，是血液吗？
You wanna try new restaurants? No, I'm not much of a foodie.
你想尝试新餐厅吗？不，我不太喜欢美食。
So what is it?
那么它是什么？
I hate it when my parents are right.
我讨厌父母说对的话。
Okay, now open.
好的，现在打开。
Thank you!
谢谢你！
You know what? I'm sorry. No, no, no, no.
你知道吗？我很抱歉。不，不，不，不。
I shouldn't be dumping all this on you.
我不该把这一切都推到你身上。
Fine. Yay!
很好。耶！
Come on, just sign the petition.
来吧，签署请愿书就行了。
Okay. Okay.
好的。好的。
Here you go. Right there.
给你，就在那里。
Ooh.
哦。
Hey, Renfield. Come on in. Hey. How are you, Goody?
嘿，Renfield。进来吧。嘿。你好吗，Goody？
Jesus.
耶稣。
Hey, Renfield. Hey, how are you?
嘿，Renfield。嘿，你好吗？
Do you mind if I smoke? Yes.
你介意我抽烟吗？介意。
But-- I mean, this can't bother you.
但是——我的意思是，这不会打扰你。
It bothers me if you're hurting yourself.
如果你伤害了自己，我会很烦恼。
Well, then awaken me.
嗯，那就叫醒我吧。
It doesn't work that way.
但事实并非如此。
You're an accountant. Do the math.
你是一名会计。算一下。
If every infected person
如果每个感染者
fed on or infected the rest of the people,
吸食或感染其他人，
the entire population would've eaten itself off the planet
地球上的所有人都会自食其力
long before Christ was even born.
早在基督诞生之前。
Only a stem can turn someone.
唯有茎干才能转动人。
Is that the sweater Tepish knit you?
这是 Tepish 给你织的毛衣吗？
Mm-hmm. It would be impolite not to wear it.
嗯嗯。不戴的话就太不礼貌了。
And it goes with everything.
它与一切都相配。
Wait till you see the one he's making you.
等着看他为你做了什么吧。
Okay, people.
好了，各位。
This is an amazing event.
这是一次令人惊奇的事件。
Except for Cisserus, we have all the stems
除了Cisserus，我们有所有的后裔
from the tri-state area.
来自三州地区。
Vadim the Russian, Ukrainian.
瓦迪姆（Vadim）俄罗斯人、乌克兰人。
- Ashwan from Kush. - Hi, Ashwan.
- 来自库什的阿什万。 - 嗨，阿什万。
- Ghuri, the Turkish stem. - Hi, Ghuri.
- Ghuri，土耳其语词干。 - 嗨，古里。
Yuppa, yuppa.
是啊，是啊。
I'd like to start by asking,
首先我想问一下，
how many of you have gotten subpoenas?
你们中有多少人收到了传票？
Excuse me.
打扰一下。
Why do not we just eat the lawyers?
我们为什么不直接吃掉律师呢？
You crazy. We can't eat all the lawyers.
你疯了。我们不可能把所有的律师都吃掉。
Why not?
为什么不呢？
Let's just say eating lawyers is out of the question.
我们就说吃律师是不可能的吧。
I know you can sense
我知道你能感觉到
that we have day players among us.
我们当中也有临时演员。
This is my granddaughter, Sarah.
这是我的孙女莎拉。
Hi, Sarah.
嗨莎拉。
And this is our friend Renfield.
这是我们的朋友 Renfield。
He's a CPA so he can help with the IRS stuff.
他是一名注册会计师，因此可以帮助处理国税局的事情。
And I understand we have a lawyer here.
据我所知我们这里有一名律师。
You absolutely do.
你当然会这么做。
How you doin'? My name is Danny.
你好吗？我叫丹尼。
Hi, Danny. And I'm from the ACLU.
你好，丹尼。我来自美国公民自由联盟。
From what I understand, you can't be forced out
据我所知，你不能被强迫离开
during the day and you don't want anyone to molest
白天，你不想被任何人骚扰
your resting places.
你的休息场所。
But the government can enter your home any time they want
但政府可以随时进入你的家
because of the Patriot Act.
因为爱国者法案。
See what's going down now
看看现在发生了什么
is that all your cell phones and your iPhones
你们所有的手机和 iPhone
and all the computers are helping them find you.
所有的计算机都在帮助他们找到你。
So I urge you not to use any of your electronic devices.
因此我劝你不要使用任何电子设备。
How will we do anything?
我们该怎么办？
How do we even stay in touch with each other?
我们怎样才能保持联系？
I used to write things down.
我过去常常把事情写下来。
Oh, yeah. Like in a datebook. Right.
哦，是的。就像记事本一样。对。
But I need my computer to tell me sunrise and sunset.
但我需要我的电脑告诉我日出和日落。
Oh, I can tell everyone that on my almanac.
哦，我可以在年历上告诉大家这一点。
Under "Sky Watch," it's got phases of the moon,
在“天空观察”下，有月相，
high tide, sunrise and sunset, and-- good Lord!
涨潮、日出、日落，还有——老天啊！
What? What is it?
啥？啥？
Total eclipse of the sun in two weeks.
两周内将发生日全食。
Hold on, hold on.
坚持住，坚持住。
2:10 to 3:40.
2:10 至 3:40。
Too bad that wasn't the exact time of our summons.
可惜那不是我们被召唤的确切时间。
If we had face time, we could use hypnotism.
如果我们有面对面交流的机会，我们可以使用催眠疗法。
No, why? That wouldn't make any difference.
不，为什么？那没什么区别。
Couldn't we just change the times of the appointments?
我们不能改变预约的时间吗？
Yeah. We could get you completely eliminated
是的。我们可以让你彻底被淘汰
from their system. We could delete and change
从他们的系统中。我们可以删除和更改
everything in their computers.
他们的计算机里的一切。
You know, I can see why
你知道，我明白为什么
you have sworn off human blood.
你已经发誓不再食用人类的鲜血。
Awesome. Do you want to join?
太棒了。你想加入吗？
How would you ladies like to be my wives?
女士们，你们愿意做我的妻子吗？
Eat me.
吃我吧。
All right. Not literally.
好吧。不是字面意思。
Oh, are you okay?
噢，你还好吗？
You were sick yesterday, too.
你昨天也病了。
Look what I got you.
看看我给你带来了什么。
Pure pharmaceutical grade.
纯医药级。
Oh, but they're so cute.
哦，但它们太可爱了。
They're not like vermin. They could be somebody's pets. Hi!
它们不像害虫。它们可能是某人的宠物。嗨！
I figured they wouldn't make you sick.
我认为它们不会让你生病。
It's nothing. I'm fine.
没什么。我很好。
It's just when I get up.
就在我起床的时候。
Quit futzing. We have to go.
别再胡闹了。我们得走了。
Oh, don't start with me.
哦，别先从我开始。
Drop waists are coming back. Yeah, says who?
低腰设计又回来了。是啊，谁说的？
I saw a picture of Keira Knightley in one.
我在一张照片里看到了凯拉奈特莉。
Yeah, right.
是的，对。
That's because Keira Knightley's in a movie.
那是因为凯拉奈特莉演了一部电影。
Ha, look at you! I know.
哈，看看你！我知道。
This was my college interview outfit.
这是我的大学面试服装。
Were you trying for a football scholarship?
您是否正在争取足球奖学金？
Ha-ha. It's the only thing I have that looks respectful.
哈哈。这是我唯一一件看起来很有礼貌的东西。
- Whoa, check it out. - I know, it's crazy.
- 哇，看看吧。 - 我知道，这很疯狂。
Mom, look! I've never seen it before.
妈妈，看！我以前从来没有见过。
Don't look directly at it, honey.
亲爱的，别直视它。
Wow, I totally forgot what it was like.
哇，我完全忘记那是什么样子的。
It's an entirely different world.
这是一个完全不同的世界。
Oh, so many women.
噢，这么多女人。
Have a nice day.
祝你今天过得愉快。
Come on, everybody. Let's go. We only have two hours.
快点，大家，我们走吧。我们只有两个小时了。
Hey, so do you know where we're going?
嘿，那么你知道我们要去哪里吗？
You will do what my accountant says.
你必须按我的会计师说的做。
It's CPA.
这是 CPA。
Okay, this is Ghuri.
好吧，这是古里。
This is file number 318.
这是文件编号318。
This Vlad Tepish.
这是 Vlad Tepish。
He was granted asylum in, um...
他被批准在……寻求庇护
1583.
1583年。
Currently married to a US citizen.
目前与美国公民结婚。
Well, four.
嗯，四个。
Yeah, that's okay.
嗯，没关系。
Child of an American fiancée.
美国未婚妻的孩子。
For an adjustment of status.
为了调整状态。
A student visa so he can matriculate at UCLA.
一份学生签证，这样他就可以在加州大学洛杉矶分校入学。
Go Bruins.
加油，棕熊队。
Yeah.
是的。
Stacy Daimer is unable to perform jury duty obligations.
斯泰西·戴默 (Stacy Daimer) 无法履行陪审义务。
Unable to perform jury duty obligations.
无法履行陪审义务。
In fact, I'll just delete them. Just delete them.
事实上，我会直接删除它们。直接删除它们。
Put the deleted names in the trash.
将已删除的名字放入垃圾箱。
Deleted names in trash.
已删除垃圾箱中的名字。
Empty the trash. Empty the trash.
清空垃圾箱。清空垃圾箱。
Ask the IT guy to remove the hard drive.
让 IT 人员移除硬盘。
Go, go, go! Excuse us, coming through!
快走，快走，快走！不好意思，我们过来了！
Joey!
乔伊！
Yeah!
是的！
Let me see. Open.
让我看看。打开。
Hold it up. Hold it up.
坚持住，坚持住。
Aw, beautiful color.
噢，颜色很漂亮。
They're having the book launch party for The Situation
他们正在举办《The Situation》新书发布会
right now on 10th. What do you say?
现在是 10 号。你说什么？
Ugh. Not worth the candle.
唉。得不偿失。
We're happy here.
我们在这里很开心。
Every A-lister in New York will be there.
纽约的每一位一线明星都会出席。
You can have whoever you want.
你可以拥有任何你想要的人。
Mm. You get tired of that.
嗯。你厌倦了。
Oh, I like this song.
哦，我喜欢这首歌。
You wanna dance. Yeah, do you?
你想跳舞吗？是的，是吗？
Yeah. Okay.
嗯，好的。
Aren't you gonna dance?
你不想跳舞吗？
Me? I don't think so.
我？我不这么认为。
I'm not very good, no. Yes, you are.
我不是很好，不是。是的，你很好。
I remember. Yeah, but I don't remember.
我记得。是的，但我不记得了。
Do you sleep with henchmen?
你跟你的追随者一起睡觉吗？
Joey had to go. His dad is bugging out.
乔伊必须走了。他爸爸出去了。
Problems at work, no doubt.
毫无疑问，工作中存在问题。
Hmm. Wonder who that could be.
嗯。不知道那人是谁。
Oh, isn't it insane?
噢，这不是太疯狂了吗？
I was dating for 25 years
我交往了 25 年
and I've never imagined to feel this way about somebody.
我从来没想过会对某人有这样的感觉。
What about you and Danny?
你和丹尼怎么样？
Mm, I never stopped loving him.
嗯，我从未停止爱他。
But his wife's sick so there's no even thinking about it.
但他的妻子病了所以他根本没考虑这件事。
I'm just happy around him.
和他在一起我很开心。
Reminds me of being hopeful.
让我想起了充满希望。
But how great would it be if we both had relationships?
但如果我们俩都有恋爱关系那该有多好？
I mean, wouldn't it be so cool--
我的意思是，这不是很酷吗——
Mott Street.
勿街。
Mott Street. Oh!
勿街。噢！
What is she doing back so soon?
她这么快就回来干什么？
I guess things didn't work out with Diego.
我猜 Diego 的事情没有成功。
Ugh. She's in Chinatown.
呃。她在唐人街。
God, just when things were going so well.
天啊，事情进展得这么顺利。
Mm.
毫米。
Oh-- oh, God.
噢——噢，天哪。
I've never seen real dead people.
我从来没有见过真正的死人。
What did you do?
你做了什么？
You know how it is
你知道情况是怎样的
when you eat Chinese.
当你吃中餐的时候
Half an hour later you're hungry again.
半小时后你又饿了。
How could you?
你怎么能这样？
Oh, I just can't stop eating.
哦，我就是停不下来吃东西。
I'm so depressed.
我好郁闷。
Why didn't he like me?
他为什么不喜欢我？
I am so much more bomb-ass than his girlfriend.
我比他的女朋友还要性感。
Maybe she wasn't a homicidal maniac.
也许她并不是一个杀人狂。
Maybe.
或许。
This is disgusting!
这太恶心了！
I know.
我知道。
I could so easily hate myself.
我很容易就恨我自己。
But just because you overdid it one day,
但只是因为有一天你做得过火了，
doesn't mean you have to be bad all weekend.
这并不意味着你整个周末都要过得不好。
What's wrong with him?
他怎么了？
Finish him off, will ya?
把他解决掉，好吗？
I said kill him.
我说杀了他。
You really can't kill.
确实不能杀人。
You guys are so useless.
你们真是没用。
Forget it.
忘了它。
Hey, can I have a fortune cookie, at least?
嘿，至少可以给我一块幸运饼干吗？
That was way too close.
那太近了。
And I didn't put in rollers.
我没放滚筒。
I'm gonna have coffin hair tomorrow.
我明天就要拥有棺材般的头发了。
I know.
我知道。
Goody, I don't think
很好，我不这么认为
I can do anything like that again.
我可以再次做任何类似的事情。
Me either.
我也是。
The world changes, we have to adapt.
世界在变化，我们必须适应。
These violent old ways
这些暴力的老方法
don't make any sense anymore.
不再有任何意义。
But she won't listen.
但她不听。
She's insane. Oh, tell me about it.
她疯了。哦，跟我说说吧。
Tepish, is there anything like a...
Tepish，有没有什么像......
Sanguine's doctor?
Sanguine 的医生？
Stacy is sick.
Stacy病了。
That's impossible. We don't get sick.
那不可能。我们不会生病。
That's what I thought,
我也是这么想的，
but every night when we get up, she vomits.
但每天晚上我们起床时，她都会呕吐。
Just how old was she when she was awakened?
她觉醒的时候到底多大？
20.
20.
And I assume there is a boyfriend.
我猜她有男朋友。
Why?
为什么？
She's not sick. She's pregnant.
她没有生病。她只是怀孕了。
So she can have a baby?
那么她可以生孩子吗？
No, the pregnancy will end by itself.
不会，妊娠会自行终止。
Unless she turns back.
除非她回头。
Like, if Cisserus dies?
比如，如果Cisserus死了呢？
Cisserus.
Cisserus
Don't you worry, hmm?
你不担心吗，嗯？
Stacy will be just fine in about a week.
大约一周后，Stacy就会康复。
They notified us about a patient having seizures
他们通知我们一名患者癫痫发作
who had a double puncture wound. When I asked who checked him in,
他身上有两处穿刺伤。当我问是谁帮他办理的住院手续时，
I went back to their surveillance cameras.
我回到他们的监控摄像头前。
Where's the body? Mount Sinai.
尸体在哪？西奈山。
Tell them we're coming. Mm-hmm.
告诉他们我们来了。嗯哼。
All right, sit down, listen to me.
好啦，坐下，听我说。
Now, I know you think I'm crazy,
现在我知道你认为我疯了，
but you have to do something for me.
但你必须为我做一件事。
Sure.
当然。
Carry this with you at all times.
随时携带它。
What? This is how you load it.
什么？这就是你装载它的方式。
Only use the silver bullets.
只使用银弹。
Only use them on what? Stacy?
只在什么地方使用它们？Stacy？
Just keep it with you.
只要随身携带即可。
Don't give me any shit.
别跟我胡扯。
When a problem comes along, like hunger, you must whip it.
当问题出现时，比如饥饿，你必须克服它。
It says this guy's a comic? He's not even funny.
据说这家伙是个喜剧演员？他一点也不好笑。
I've never seen him in anything.
我从来没有见过他演任何角色。
What's on?
正在发生什么？
"Assholes Insult People More Talented Than Them."
“混蛋侮辱比他们更有才华的人。”
"The Excessively '80s Countdown."
“过度的 80 年代倒计时。”
Oh, show Goody.
哦，展示一下 Goody。
Oh.
哦。
So my father decided to give me this.
所以我父亲决定把这个给我。
Hmm. That's weird.
嗯。这很奇怪。
Oh, careful. It's got silver bullets in it.
噢，小心点。这里面有银弹。
What's he thinking?
他在想什么？
He's got more paranoid
他变得更加偏执
since he saw the footage from the hospital.
因为他看到了医院的录像。
What footage?
什么镜头？
This guy just seemed to fly from a cab to the front door.
这家伙似乎刚从出租车飞到前门。
I'm such an idiot.
我真是个白痴。
Why didn't I look for surveillance cameras?
我为什么没找监控摄像头？
Wait a minute, you-- No, no. We didn't do anything.
等一下，你——不，不。我们什么也没做。
It was-- it was our stem, Cisserus.
它是—它是我们的茎，西塞罗斯。
She's a monster.
她是一个怪物。
She's gonna louse it up for all of us.
她会把我们大家的处境都搞糟的。
Don't trip. We'll talk to Tepish.
别绊倒。我们会和特皮什谈谈。
Oh, I saw him after work
哦，我下班后见到他了
and he said you'll be feeling better soon.
他说你很快就会感觉好起来。
You're just pregnant.
你刚刚怀孕。
What?
什么？
I'm pregnant? We're gonna have a baby.
我怀孕了？我们要有个孩子了。
I'm pregnant!
我怀孕了！
Oh, my God!
我的天啊！
Oh, I can't believe this. I'm pregnant?
哦，我简直不敢相信。我怀孕了？
You want a baby?
你想要个孩子吗？
Well...
出色地...
yeah.
是的。
I'm over 40. How many more chances am I gonna get?
我已经40多岁了。我还有多少次机会？
And besides, I'll make a kick-ass father.
此外，我还会成为一个出色的父亲。
All right.
好的。
Forget cell phones, forget iPhones,
忘掉手机，忘掉 iPhone，
forget PowerBooks, forget iPads.
忘记 PowerBooks，忘记 iPad。
Yay.
耶。
Now I can do everything I want
现在我可以做任何我想做的事
with my iPad Mini.
和我的 iPad Mini 一起。
That looks just like your phone.
这看起来就像你的手机。
But it doesn't make calls.
但它不能拨打电话。
I got my tweets, I got my e-mails,
我收到了推文，收到了电子邮件，
I got my friends, I got my alerts, I got--
我得到了我的朋友，我得到了我的警报，我得到了......
So as the day progresses, you can read
因此，随着一天的进展，你可以阅读
thousands of unsolicited messages,
数以千计的未经请求的信息，
advertisements, and the mindless brain vomit of acquaintances?
广告和熟人的无脑胡言乱语？
Someone sounds hormonal.
有人听起来很有活力。
Maybe you're pregnant, too!
也许你也怀孕了！
So annoying.
真烦人。
You have to keep learning to use new crap
你必须不断学习使用新东西
that doesn't actually do anything better
这实际上并没有起到什么更好的作用
than the old crap, which is incompatible with the new crap,
比旧的垃圾更糟糕，因为旧的垃圾与新的垃圾不相容，
all so you can have blogs and watch fake teenagers
所有这些都是为了让你拥有博客和观看假青少年
and real housewives?
和真正的家庭主妇？
And it's all happening too fast
一切都发生得太快了
and I'm tired.
我累了。
I'm just sick and tired of it all.
我对这一切都感到厌烦。
It's okay.
没关系。
We don't have to get the iPad Minis.
我们没必要购买 iPad Mini。
No, I'm sorry...
不，很抱歉……
Look. Only a couple stations, but they had Groucho Marx.
瞧。只有几个电台，但他们有格鲁乔·马克斯。
No, that's not Groucho.
不，那不是格劳乔。
Groucho was the mustache guy.
格劳乔是个留着小胡子的男人。
Yeah, he had glasses and a cigar.
是的，他戴着眼镜，抽着雪茄。
Yeah, a cigar and glasses.
是的，一支雪茄和一副眼镜。
You'll split $25 between you. Are you ready?
你们将平分 25 美元。你准备好了吗？
Yes. Who is buried in Grant's Tomb?
是的。格兰特墓里埋葬的是谁？
Were people really that stupid?
难道人们真的那么愚蠢吗？
No, that's what he'd ask when he felt bad
不，那是他心情不好时才会问的问题
and wanted to give 'em a few bucks.
并想给他们几块钱。
Is Grant's Tomb in New York?
格兰特之墓在纽约吗？
No. No. Yeah. Yeah.
不，不，是的，是的。
Have any of you ever been there?
你们有人去过那里吗？
No. No.
不不。
- That's it. - What?
- 就是这样。 - 什么？
God, the place no New Yorker ever goes.
天哪，纽约人从来不去的地方。
Of course, Cisserus would want a monument.
当然，Cisserus想要一座纪念碑。
And it's got a tomb.
它有一座坟墓。
Oh, my God. You're probably right.
哦天哪。你可能是对的。
Come on.
快点。
Show me again. Yeah, here.
再给我看看。是的，在这里。
I guess I totally can tell, but it's--
我想我完全能看出来，但是——
it's like, I don't know. I always thought you'd be
就像，我不知道。我一直以为你会
the first one to have a baby. Is that weird?
第一个生孩子。这很奇怪吗？
But now that it's happening-- Listen.
但既然它已经发生了——听着。
You have to decide something independent of me or Joey.
你必须独立于我或乔伊来决定一些事情。
This baby won't survive in your condition.
按照你的情况，这个婴儿无法存活。
If you want it, you have to turn back.
如果你想要它，你就必须回头。
How does that even--
那怎么可能——
Cisserus would have to be killed.
西塞罗斯必须被杀死。
That's right.
这是正确的。
I'd be in my '40s.
那时我已经40多岁了。
But I'd be a mom.
但我会成为一名妈妈。
You'd be older, too. I know.
你也会老一些。我知道。
I can't decide for the both of us.
我无法替我们俩做决定。
How do you feel about not being young anymore?
您对于自己不再年轻有何感受？
Which part--
哪一部分——
running around to clubs and dating idiots?
到处跑俱乐部和白痴约会？
Would be nice not to have to fake all the references.
如果不需要伪造所有的参考资料就好了。
Ugh. Like acting nostalgic over
呃。就像怀旧一样
"Hey, Arnold" instead of "Happy Days."
“嘿，阿诺德”而不是“快乐的时光”。
Not to mention the slang, "BTW."
更不用说俚语“BTW”了。
And the clothes and the music.
还有衣服和音乐。
Staying young is getting old.
保持年轻就是变老。
Plus, we'll have a baby.
另外，我们还会有一个孩子。
What are we even talking about? We can't kill Cisserus.
我们到底在说什么？我们不能杀死西塞罗斯。
She's lasted hundreds of years.
她已经存在了几百年。
But that's because nobody knew where she was.
但那是因为没人知道她在哪里。
But she's very sturdy.
但她非常坚强。
And let's face it, we're wimps.
让我们面对现实吧，我们是懦夫。
Yeah, but she's sloppy. And conceited.
是啊，但她很邋遢，而且自负。
And we'll call in the heavy-hitters.
我们将召集重量级人物。
Who?
WHO？
Your future father-in-law.
你未来的岳父。
I just have to do one thing first.
我只需要先做一件事。
You said for a little more time, you'd do anything.
你说过，只要再多一点时间，你愿意做任何事。
Did you mean it? Of course, but what can I do?
你是认真的吗？当然，但我能做什么呢？
Would you change your schedule and stay up later
你会改变你的日程安排并熬夜吗
and promise to let her only have animals?
并承诺让她只养动物？
Now, wait a minute. Can you keep her alive?
现在，等一下。你能让她活下去吗？
Not exactly alive. But not dead?
不算活着，但也不至于死吧？
I can't but he can.
我不能，但他可以。
It's up to you. Yeah.
这取决于你。是的。
Yeah, I can't lose her.
是啊，我不能失去她。
I need privacy to do this.
我需要隐私才能做这件事。
Ah.
啊。
That's enough. It doesn't take that long.
够了。不需要那么长时间。
Your wife is very sweet.
你的妻子很可爱。
Yeah. So, uh...
是的。那么，呃……
I am just wondering,
我只是想知道，
are you guys getting along, or, uh...
你们相处得好吗，或者，呃……
any chance of breaking up in the future?
将来还有分手的可能吗？
Danny.
丹尼。
Thank you.
谢谢。
You're welcome.
不客气。
Come on, open up.
来吧，打开吧。
Who's there? I'm a friend of your son.
谁呀？我是你儿子的朋友。
I wanna help you. You want to help me?
我想帮助你。你想帮助我吗？
I've got some news for you, Grandpa.
我有消息告诉你，爷爷。
Did you say Grandpa?
你是說爷爷嗎？
I thought all victims turned into vampires or died.
我以为所有受害者都会变成吸血鬼或死亡。
I've never heard of anyone turning back.
我从没听说有人回头。
Well, I've never known anyone firsthand.
嗯，我从来没有直接认识过任何人。
But apparently, if you're young enough--
但显然，如果你足够年轻——
those are useless on a stem.
这些在茎上是无用的。
Are you really sure this isn't just Joey's rebelliousness?
你真的确定这不仅仅是乔伊的叛逆吗？
I mean, do they seem serious?
我的意思是，他们看起来是认真的吗？
Well, I've never seen Stacy like this before.
嗯，我以前从来没见过Stacy这样。
And he's so excited to be a dad.
他对于成为一名父亲感到非常兴奋。
I believe they really are in love.
我相信他们真的相爱。
When did you awaken?
你什麼時候醒的？
1841.
1841年。
I survived a feeding and begged her to turn me.
我吃饱饭后还活着，并恳求她把我转过来。
You wanted to become a vampire?
你想成为吸血鬼吗？
It was the lesser of two infections.
这是两次感染中较轻的一次。
In 1840, there was an epidemic of cholera
1840 年，霍乱流行
in lower Manhattan.
位于曼哈顿下城。
It was a painful and degrading death.
这是一种痛苦且有辱人格的死亡。
My husband and sisters had all passed.
我的丈夫和姐妹都去世了。
But, miraculously, my children were fine.
但奇迹般地，我的孩子们都安然无恙。
Not to be indelicate, but I had digestive rumblings
不是不礼貌，但我有消化不良的症状
that I knew were the early symptoms,
我知道这是早期症状，
and orphans did not fare well in those days.
在那个年代，孤儿的境遇并不好。
So did your kids survive?
那么你的孩子幸存了吗？
My son lived to the ripe old age of 63.
我的儿子活到了63岁高龄。
And my daughter married Peter Meester,
我女儿嫁给了彼得·梅斯特，
and lived to be 99.
并活到了99岁。
Unprecedented at the time.
在当时是史无前例的。
Well, not many elderly people had strong young mothers
嗯，没有多少老人有坚强的年轻母亲
to look out for them.
去照顾他们。
After the grandchildren, it would've been hard
有了孙子以后，生活就变得艰难了
to stay in their lives and not scare them.
留在他们生活中并且不会吓到他们。
- Did you get that? - Got it.
- 你明白了吗？ - 知道了。
You know, the only surefire way is to behead her.
你知道，唯一万无一失的方法就是斩首她。
Everything else might just piss her off.
其他一切也许只会让她生气。
And when Cisserus is dead,
当Cisserus死后，
Stacy will be a normal girl.
Stacy将会是一个正常的女孩。
Normal for Stacy.
对 Stacy 来说很正常。
But, what happens to you, then?
但那之后你会怎么样呢？
I saved my kids.
我救了我的孩子们。
Let's go save yours.
让我们去拯救你的。
Here you go. Here's your family tree.
给你。这是你的家谱。
Your living descendants.
您的在世后代。
A great-great-great-great grandson.
一位曾曾曾孙。
A drug addict. Incarcerated.
一名吸毒者。被监禁。
Four doctors. One in Doctors Without Borders.
四位医生。其中一位来自无国界医生组织。
Two professors, four teachers,
两位教授，四位老师，
and in the House of Representatives,
在众议院，
Jane Rutherford, who chairs several committees.
简·卢瑟福 (Jane Rutherford)，担任多个委员会主席。
She looks like you.
她看起来像你。
Thank you.
谢谢。
All right, leave the guns.
好吧，把枪留下。
Bring the axes, hatchets, blades.
带上斧头、短柄斧和刀片。
All right, let's go get this dried up bitch.
好啦，我们赶紧去找这个干瘪的婊子吧。
Well, I don't go to those places much, either.
嗯，我也不经常去那些地方。
But it just shows you can meet someone really nice.
但这说明你能遇见一个非常好的人。
Well, I never go to those places, so...
嗯，我从来没有去过那些地方，所以......
I can't believe I met you, though.
但我真不敢相信我遇见了你。
You are beautiful. You're so sweet.
你很美。你很可爱。
Would you like to sit? Oh, would I?
你想坐吗？哦，我想坐。
Nice here. Isn't it?
这里很不错。不是吗？
Oh.
哦。
Isn't your wife worried about
你妻子不担心
where you are so late?
你这么晚来哪儿了？
She's on a trip and what she don't know won't hurt her.
她正在旅行，她不知道的事情不会伤害她。
Aren't you a bad boy?
你不是一个坏男孩吗？
I can be very bad.
我可能非常糟糕。
So what does a dirty boy like you do for a living?
那么像你这样一个邋遢的男孩靠什么谋生呢？
I'm a dentist.
我是一名牙医。
You're a dentist?
你是牙医？
What a lucky break.
真是幸运的突破。
Because I have something I'm really concerned about.
因为我有非常关心的事情。
Can I show you?
我可以演示给你看吗？
I've never seen anything like that in my--
我从来没有见过这样的事情......
Oh, no! No!
噢不！不！
Run! Get out of here!
快跑！离开这里！
You asshole.
你这个混蛋。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
You bad girls.
你们这些坏女孩。
I am very disappointed in you.
我对你很失望。
After all I've done for you,
在我为你做了这么多之后，
this is how you pay me back?
这就是你偿还我的方式？
Are you okay?
你還沒有事嗎？
Who treats their stem like this?
谁会这样对待自己的茎？
Those needed gunpowder!
那些需要火药！
Duck!
鸭子！
Oh, my God. We did it.
哦天哪，我们成功了。
No. You guys, we have to get her into the tomb.
不，你们几个，我们必须把她弄进坟墓里。
Help me. Okay, okay.
帮帮我。好的，好的。
Argh.
啊。
When did my ass get so flat?
我的屁股什么时候变得这么扁平了？
Can I just say-- ow!
我只能说——哎哟！
Wait-- what are we gonna do about the body?
等一下——我们该怎么处理尸体？
Oh, it'll die in a minute.
哦，它一会儿就会死。
Where were you?
当时你在哪里？
What? You asked me to get a chainsaw.
什么？你让我去拿电锯。
I get halfway here and realize it needs gasoline.
我走到一半才意识到它需要汽油。
Do you know where to get gasoline
你知道哪里可以买到汽油吗
at 4:00 in the morning?
凌晨四点？
Why didn't you get it where you got the saw?
为什么你不把它拿到你拿到锯子的地方呢？
Because I thought you plugged them in.
因为我以为你已经把它们插上了。
What am I, a lumberjack?
我是什么？伐木工人？
In the forest, you're plugging things in?
在森林里，你正在插电吗？
- Yes, like a hairdryer or a-- - Joey!
- 是的，像吹风机或者—— - 乔伊！
Come on! Come on! I don't believe this.
得了吧！得了吧！我不相信。
Hurry! Hurry.
快点！快点。
Okay, close it...
好的，关闭它...
Whoa. Okay, let's go.
哇哦。好，我们走吧。
You feel anything?
你感觉到什么了吗？
No.
不。
Wait.
等待。
That's it?
就是这样？
You've aged 20 years?
你已经老了20岁吗？
Well, I didn't drink, smoke, do drugs, or sunbathe.
嗯，我没有喝酒、抽烟、吸毒、也没有做日光浴。
Oh, well, maybe your genes just aren't as good.
哦，好吧，也许你的基因不太好。
But with Botox and laser resurfacing...
但是通过肉毒杆菌和激光换肤...
Don't tell me you lied about your age.
别告诉我你撒谎了你的年龄。
Oh, come on.
哦，来吧。
Who the hell names their kid Goody anymore?
现在还有谁会给自己的孩子取名古迪 (Goody) 呢？
You won't get any older, will you?
你不会变老了，是吗？
It's okay.
没关系。
I've been around long enough.
我已经在这里待够久了。
I'm tired.
我累了。
I should've known.
我早该知道的。
Every time I turned on the History Channel,
每次我打开历史频道，
all I saw was stuff about Hitler.
我看到的都是有关希特勒的东西。
Don't be sad. I was gonna go into the sun before I met you.
别难过。在遇见你之前，我本想走进阳光里。
You showed me how to have fun.
你告诉我如何享受乐趣。
Is there anything you want?
有什么你想要的吗？
Yes.
是的。
I don't wanna be here.
我不想待在这儿。
I want to be in the center of things.
我想成为事物的中心。
Let's go.
我们走吧。
You all right?
你还好吗？
You all right? How do you feel?
你还好吗？感觉怎么样？
Hungry.
饥饿的。
How about one of those pretzel things?
吃点椒盐卷饼怎么样？
Joey, can you go get one of those pretzel things?
乔伊，你能去买点椒盐卷饼吗？
Of course. Thanks.
当然。谢谢。
Goody. Goody.
太好了。太好了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Oh!
哦！
Hey, I saw that.
嘿，我看到了。
What? She looked at me. I wasn't doing anything.
什么？她看着我。我什么也没做。
Need I remind you that I gave you
我需要提醒你我给了你
the best years of my life? Best years of my life.
我一生中最美好的时光？我一生中最美好的时光。
Yeah, and I'm not talking five, 10 years here.
是的，我说的不是五年、十年。
We're talking infinity.
我们正在谈论无限。
Do you have any idea what that's like?
你知道那是什么感觉吗？
I'm starting to get an idea.
我开始有了一个想法。
All right, Goody. Watch this.
好的，Goody。看这个。
Too frightening.
太可怕了。
Is it too frightening?
是不是太恐怖了？
Bleh!
废话！
Well, you got Grandpa that time.
嗯，那时你有爷爷了。